[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Their money, their jobs or my brother's health?", "question_tokens": ["Their", "money", ",", "their", "jobs", "or", "my", "brother", "'s", "health", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "The real story behind all those scandals.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "real", "story", "behind", "all", "those", "scandals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "As we approach the start of this trial, what are your feelings?", "question_tokens": ["As", "we", "approach", "the", "start", "of", "this", "trial", ",", "what", "are", "your", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "My feelings are, just as well as the family, the truth is going to come out.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "feelings", "are", ",", "just", "as", "well", "as", "the", "family", ",", "the", "truth", "is", "going", "to", "come", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Do you think that Conrad Murray was solely responsible for your brother's death?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "Conrad", "Murray", "was", "solely", "responsible", "for", "your", "brother", "'s", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "My gut feeling is the fact that Conrad was present during his death, there's a lot of questions to be answered.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "gut", "feeling", "is", "the", "fact", "that", "Conrad", "was", "present", "during", "his", "death", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "questions", "to", "be", "answered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, I think that, first of all, being a cardiologist and not an anesthesiologist, there's a big difference.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "being", "a", "cardiologist", "and", "not", "an", "anesthesiologist", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "big", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Do you think that's possible?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I really don't know but I do know that it's a difference between Demerol and Propofol.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "but", "I", "do", "know", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "difference", "between", "Demerol", "and", "Propofol", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Is Propofol considered by most physicians to be an anesthetic, rather than just a sleeping pill?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Propofol", "considered", "by", "most", "physicians", "to", "be", "an", "anesthetic", ",", "rather", "than", "just", "a", "sleeping", "pill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I really don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "When did you see Conrad Murray that night in the hospital?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "see", "Conrad", "Murray", "that", "night", "in", "the", "hospital", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I saw Conrad when I first went to the hospital.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "Conrad", "when", "I", "first", "went", "to", "the", "hospital", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Did he look guilty?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "look", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "His behavior, how he was acting.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "behavior", ",", "how", "he", "was", "acting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Did he look concerned?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "look", "concerned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Did you talk to him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "talk", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", ":", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Did he say anything to any of the family?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "say", "anything", "to", "any", "of", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "He wanted to come in, I guess, and say his -- something to my mother and his condolences or something but I felt uneasy with him.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "wanted", "to", "come", "in", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "and", "say", "his", "--", "something", "to", "my", "mother", "and", "his", "condolences", "or", "something", "but", "I", "felt", "uneasy", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Did you know that he'd been with Michael that night?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "that", "he", "'d", "been", "with", "Michael", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I found out, yes, that he was with Michael.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "out", ",", "yes", ",", "that", "he", "was", "with", "Michael", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"], "TIME": ["that night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Which tapes were erased?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "tapes", "were", "erased", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "The surveillance tapes were erased.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "surveillance", "tapes", "were", "erased", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "They're all gone?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "all", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, some of the tapes were erased to the whereabouts who would come in and out during the time, at the house.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "some", "of", "the", "tapes", "were", "erased", "to", "the", "whereabouts", "who", "would", "come", "in", "and", "out", "during", "the", "time", ",", "at", "the", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Who do you think would erase it?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "would", "erase", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "They were in the hands of the police department.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "in", "the", "hands", "of", "the", "police", "department", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "And how often did you talk to Michael?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "often", "did", "you", "talk", "to", "Michael", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "We spoke to him not that much during rehearsal.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "spoke", "to", "him", "not", "that", "much", "during", "rehearsal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "``", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "''", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Do you know how long he had been given Propofol?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "long", "he", "had", "been", "given", "Propofol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "When -- when \"This Is It\" there was a lot of footage that was taken out that no one saw and because that was the edit before the edit.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "--", "when", "``", "This", "Is", "It", "''", "there", "was", "a", "lot", "of", "footage", "that", "was", "taken", "out", "that", "no", "one", "saw", "and", "because", "that", "was", "the", "edit", "before", "the", "edit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "I mean what is the stuff we didn't see?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "is", "the", "stuff", "we", "did", "n't", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, things that we noticed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "things", "that", "we", "noticed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "-- of knocking somebody out for the purposes of sleep?", "question_tokens": ["--", "of", "knocking", "somebody", "out", "for", "the", "purposes", "of", "sleep", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "And plus, he's lived all this time doing Demerol and sleeping pills and also, pain pills, but the symptoms from Propofol is like no one knew that he was -- the public didn't know he was complaining about his body.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "plus", ",", "he", "'s", "lived", "all", "this", "time", "doing", "Demerol", "and", "sleeping", "pills", "and", "also", ",", "pain", "pills", ",", "but", "the", "symptoms", "from", "Propofol", "is", "like", "no", "one", "knew", "that", "he", "was", "--", "the", "public", "did", "n't", "know", "he", "was", "complaining", "about", "his", "body", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Is there any evidence that you've seen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "evidence", "that", "you", "'ve", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I really don't know, but --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "but", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What is the theory that you think about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "theory", "that", "you", "think", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Our belief is that we knew he was doing prescription drugs to sleep and pain.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "belief", "is", "that", "we", "knew", "he", "was", "doing", "prescription", "drugs", "to", "sleep", "and", "pain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "The family?", "question_tokens": ["The", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "No -- no, these are people that were around him.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--", "no", ",", "these", "are", "people", "that", "were", "around", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$15 million"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Are these side effects that you have identified?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "side", "effects", "that", "you", "have", "identified", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "These are symptoms of that because of the fact that it was administered in him outside of a hospital setting, the person wasn't adequate enough to do this, and the fact that the night that he died, he was -- he had just arranged a $15 million payment on a house.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "symptoms", "of", "that", "because", "of", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "was", "administered", "in", "him", "outside", "of", "a", "hospital", "setting", ",", "the", "person", "was", "n't", "adequate", "enough", "to", "do", "this", ",", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "night", "that", "he", "died", ",", "he", "was", "--", "he", "had", "just", "arranged", "a", "$", "15", "million", "payment", "on", "a", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Is that possible?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Whether it's possible or not, being a doctor, you take an oath.", "answer_tokens": ["Whether", "it", "'s", "possible", "or", "not", ",", "being", "a", "doctor", ",", "you", "take", "an", "oath", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "These are people working for AEG?", "question_tokens": ["These", "are", "people", "working", "for", "AEG", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "These are people working for AEG, working for him, working for the show.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "people", "working", "for", "AEG", ",", "working", "for", "him", ",", "working", "for", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How many of the people directly around him at the time that he died, do you think, are culpable for a form of responsibility for his death?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "the", "people", "directly", "around", "him", "at", "the", "time", "that", "he", "died", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "are", "culpable", "for", "a", "form", "of", "responsibility", "for", "his", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "See, that's the question I have.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "question", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Why do you think they didn't?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "they", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Because they wanted the show to go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "they", "wanted", "the", "show", "to", "go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["tens of billions of dollars"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "It's not in their interest to raise any alarm bells about his health, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "in", "their", "interest", "to", "raise", "any", "alarm", "bells", "about", "his", "health", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "No, because the fact that, still, if you have tens of billions of dollars, you still want more but this was an event that was going to put money in everybody's pockets but at the same time, his health was ignored.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "the", "fact", "that", ",", "still", ",", "if", "you", "have", "tens", "of", "billions", "of", "dollars", ",", "you", "still", "want", "more", "but", "this", "was", "an", "event", "that", "was", "going", "to", "put", "money", "in", "everybody", "'s", "pockets", "but", "at", "the", "same", "time", ",", "his", "health", "was", "ignored", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Was it the same kind of body that you would expect?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "the", "same", "kind", "of", "body", "that", "you", "would", "expect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Or this simply just not going to be enough evidence?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "this", "simply", "just", "not", "going", "to", "be", "enough", "evidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "To tell you the truth, Piers, it's -- the defense is going to try to paint my brother out to be even most horrible person and he wasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "tell", "you", "the", "truth", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "the", "defense", "is", "going", "to", "try", "to", "paint", "my", "brother", "out", "to", "be", "even", "most", "horrible", "person", "and", "he", "was", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Were any of the family attend the trial?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "any", "of", "the", "family", "attend", "the", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Will you get out?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "get", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Every day?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I'm going to try to be there as much as I can, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "try", "to", "be", "there", "as", "much", "as", "I", "can", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How do you think you'll feel when you see Conrad Murray standing there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "feel", "when", "you", "see", "Conrad", "Murray", "standing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I don't feel good about him before I knew him so I'm kind of feel the same way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "feel", "good", "about", "him", "before", "I", "knew", "him", "so", "I", "'m", "kind", "of", "feel", "the", "same", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "I mean did you lose peace of mind getting the way you've gotten?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "did", "you", "lose", "peace", "of", "mind", "getting", "the", "way", "you", "'ve", "gotten", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "No, because we've always known that this was just an illusion.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "we", "'ve", "always", "known", "that", "this", "was", "just", "an", "illusion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Wacko Jacko"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And so he played up to a lot of the things, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "he", "played", "up", "to", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "things", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Not so much of the Wacko Jacko.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "so", "much", "of", "the", "Wacko", "Jacko", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "How did you feel as his brother?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "as", "his", "brother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Michael wasn't -- he was very, very much normal.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "was", "n't", "--", "he", "was", "very", ",", "very", "much", "normal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Your father was a tough guy, though, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "father", "was", "a", "tough", "guy", ",", "though", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "My father was tough, but that's still love, because you care to discipline your child and to show them the right path to take.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "father", "was", "tough", ",", "but", "that", "'s", "still", "love", ",", "because", "you", "care", "to", "discipline", "your", "child", "and", "to", "show", "them", "the", "right", "path", "to", "take", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "As his big brother, what is the truth about Michael's skin color change over the years?", "question_tokens": ["As", "his", "big", "brother", ",", "what", "is", "the", "truth", "about", "Michael", "'s", "skin", "color", "change", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Michael --", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Was any part of him wishing he wasn't so black?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "any", "part", "of", "him", "wishing", "he", "was", "n't", "so", "black", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "How did you see that impact on him as a human being?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "see", "that", "impact", "on", "him", "as", "a", "human", "being", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Well, I do know that he wanted that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "know", "that", "he", "wanted", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "What was -- what was your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "--", "what", "was", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "No, but I -- I think he -- he wanted to change the way he looked because he wanted to improve things.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "--", "I", "think", "he", "--", "he", "wanted", "to", "change", "the", "way", "he", "looked", "because", "he", "wanted", "to", "improve", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", ":", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ":", "RB", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "RB", "CC", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "He comes -- is he about -- was he just a perfectionist?", "question_tokens": ["He", "comes", "--", "is", "he", "about", "--", "was", "he", "just", "a", "perfectionist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "He -- he -- I think in his mind, he had something that he was going after and -- but -- but these things -- once -- once you start, you get caught up into it and then you want to do a little here and there.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "he", "--", "I", "think", "in", "his", "mind", ",", "he", "had", "something", "that", "he", "was", "going", "after", "and", "--", "but", "--", "but", "these", "things", "--", "once", "--", "once", "you", "start", ",", "you", "get", "caught", "up", "into", "it", "and", "then", "you", "want", "to", "do", "a", "little", "here", "and", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Bashir", "Michael"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "When you watched that, what did you feel about that interview?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watched", "that", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Well, first of all, Martin Bashir needs to be slapped and he never should have been around Michael.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Martin", "Bashir", "needs", "to", "be", "slapped", "and", "he", "never", "should", "have", "been", "around", "Michael", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "CD", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "And -- and see, why this -- there's a question for us, why does people in the media want to say the most horrible things about someone, knowing that they have all the right intentions to do good?", "question_tokens": ["And", "--", "and", "see", ",", "why", "this", "--", "there", "'s", "a", "question", "for", "us", ",", "why", "does", "people", "in", "the", "media", "want", "to", "say", "the", "most", "horrible", "things", "about", "someone", ",", "knowing", "that", "they", "have", "all", "the", "right", "intentions", "to", "do", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "VB", ",", "WRB", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I guess the answer, if I'm putting my media hat back on, because I worked in newspapers at the time of all that, is that it's not normal -- I use that word in, you know, just in a straightforward way -- for a guy of, say, 44, to be sharing a bed with a boy of 12.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "the", "answer", ",", "if", "I", "'m", "putting", "my", "media", "hat", "back", "on", ",", "because", "I", "worked", "in", "newspapers", "at", "the", "time", "of", "all", "that", ",", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "normal", "--", "I", "use", "that", "word", "in", ",", "you", "know", ",", "just", "in", "a", "straightforward", "way", "--", "for", "a", "guy", "of", ",", "say", ",", "44", ",", "to", "be", "sharing", "a", "bed", "with", "a", "boy", "of", "12", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 516, "question": "But how do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "-- or the media --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "or", "the", "media", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I just --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I just guess -- I don't anybody like that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "guess", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "anybody", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "But do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Was Michael too innocent for this modern world, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "Michael", "too", "innocent", "for", "this", "modern", "world", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "You really believe that, that he was just from a different era?", "question_tokens": ["You", "really", "believe", "that", ",", "that", "he", "was", "just", "from", "a", "different", "era", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "He was from the era that -- that we were from.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "from", "the", "era", "that", "--", "that", "we", "were", "from", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "How are his three children?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "his", "three", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Very, very, very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", ",", "very", ",", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Do they -- do they use the Internet and stuff like that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "--", "do", "they", "use", "the", "Internet", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "They do, but we don't like it.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "do", ",", "but", "we", "do", "n't", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Do any of them show any signs of wanting to follow in Michael's footsteps as entertainers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "any", "of", "them", "show", "any", "signs", "of", "wanting", "to", "follow", "in", "Michael", "'s", "footsteps", "as", "entertainers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "They're very much into film.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "very", "much", "into", "film", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Who do you think has the -- the most chance of being a successful actor or actress?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "has", "the", "--", "the", "most", "chance", "of", "being", "a", "successful", "actor", "or", "actress", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Well, Paris is -- is -- is a star.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Paris", "is", "--", "is", "--", "is", "a", "star", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Or does the good that you've enjoyed from all this outweigh the -- the bad?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "the", "good", "that", "you", "'ve", "enjoyed", "from", "all", "this", "outweigh", "the", "--", "the", "bad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "The good definitely outweighs the bad.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "good", "definitely", "outweighs", "the", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110915pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "When this trial starts, if you feel that he's getting unfairly trashed in there, how are you going to deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "this", "trial", "starts", ",", "if", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "'s", "getting", "unfairly", "trashed", "in", "there", ",", "how", "are", "you", "going", "to", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Michael's done so much good and so many good deeds that he's well protected.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "'s", "done", "so", "much", "good", "and", "so", "many", "good", "deeds", "that", "he", "'s", "well", "protected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]